<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Neil Spink</title><link>https://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Neil Spink</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100days.ink — A Commitment Engine</title><link>https://example.org/posts/100days/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/100days/</guid><description>I’ve been building 100days.ink, a small app with a big purpose:
help people commit to something for 100 days and actually follow through.
The rules are simple:
Write down your 100-day commitment. Pick a start or end date. Decide if it’s private, public, or shared with the community. Put some skin in the game — tip from $2 to $147. That’s it. No feeds. No distractions. Just you versus the next 100 days.</description></item><item><title>Recaptures: a one‑minute screen capture journal (C#)</title><link>https://example.org/posts/recaptures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/recaptures/</guid><description>A tiny Windows utility that snapshots your screen every minute and ships it to storage—useful for a visual work log.</description></item><item><title>Building a Mood Barometer: The IoT Workshop at Swiss Re</title><link>https://example.org/posts/mood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/mood/</guid><description>Building a Mood Barometer: The IoT Workshop at Swiss Re n early 2020, I hosted a hands-on IoT workshop at Swiss Re. The challenge? Build a mood barometer — a physical dial that reflects the emotional &amp;ldquo;weather&amp;rdquo; of a space.
Each team flashed an ESP32, wrote Arduino code to read mood values over HTTP or MQTT, and moved a dial to match. No soldering — just ESP32 boards, stepper motors, and a magnet sensor wired up to detect calibration points.</description></item><item><title>Map the metadata of your YAML</title><link>https://example.org/posts/yaml-dredger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/yaml-dredger/</guid><description>yaml-dredger I thought it would be useful to analyze the structure of YAML files at scale.
YAML gets used for everything — APIs, configurations, Kubernetes, data specs — and often no one really knows what&amp;rsquo;s in the files. This script crawls a folder of YAML and gives you a kind of map: what entities exist, what fields they have, and where they show up.
It&amp;rsquo;s not pretty — but it works.</description></item><item><title>Subutai P2P Cloud + Minecraft Hosting</title><link>https://example.org/posts/subutai-minecraft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/subutai-minecraft/</guid><description>Why Subutai’s P2P cloud grabbed me and how I wrote a Minecraft hosting blueprint to be part of it.</description></item></channel></rss>